<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>onboarding on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/tags/onboarding/</link><description>Recent content in onboarding on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/tags/onboarding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Onboarding</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</guid><description>The first few months are crucial to the success of the new hire. The newcomer will either buy in by investing their time and attention or treat the company as a paycheck printer, working hard enough not to get fired.
Buddy helps to make onboarding experience engaging, yet well-organized and structured. Work-related information, served in tiny bits in the issue-tracker, facilitates the smooth transition to work culture of a Hygge company.</description></item><item><title>Personal Project</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-project/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-project/</guid><description>Every newcomer&amp;rsquo;s journey at Hygge Company starts with a personal project. Personal project is a private space to set and track personal milestones. It can take different forms - personal repository or a dashboard, depends on an issue tracker that Hygge company uses.
Enjoy making daily to-do lists? Want to test how markdown on GitHub works? Planning to learn Python from a colleague? Personal project is a powerful tool that satisfies all those needs.</description></item><item><title>Buddy guidelines</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</guid><description>Visiting another country or hiking an unknown trail all by yourself definitely has its advantages. But if you want to get to know all the local tips and tricks, discover the best view-points and learn fast and safe ways up, you look for local guides.
The same is when you join a new team. A new employee’s onboarding experience is greatly enhanced by buddy who acts as a local guide.</description></item><item><title>Personal Growth</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire people not only because they are useful now, but also because they believe in their potential.
Working in a Hygge Company provides an opportunity for extremely efficient and, in many cases, very accelerated, career growth. In particular, it provides an opportunity to broaden your skill set well outside the narrow constraints that careers can have at most other companies. There is no red tape, allowing you to tailor your own “growth ladder”.</description></item></channel></rss>