<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/</link><description>Recent content in About on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Async</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</guid><description>To get things done, Hygge Companies rely on detailed documentation and atomic iterations that are visible to everyone through issue trackers like GitHub. Mastering this asynchronous workflow is vital to avoiding dysfunction. This is why Hygge companies prefer GitHub issues to chats and video calls. This also means that employees need to ensure that all conclusions made during offline conversations are recorded in GitHub, so that everyone at any time can follow your thought process.</description></item><item><title>Challenge Program</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</guid><description>Challenge program is a perfect tool to discover hidden talent through autonomously vetting potential employees and interns at the start of the hiring process. They consist of issues that can be solved without any access to company resources and require the participants to manage their own work. These projects give interested individuals a chance to prove themselves, learn a bit about our company &amp;amp; products, and produce a useful result in the process.</description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</guid><description>The importance of feedback Human beings are social by nature. Our inclination to change our behavior in reliance upon feedback from our fellows is a primary evolutionary adaptation mechanism. Feedback is our relationship with the world and the world’s relationship with us, it’s how we make an impact on other people. Working in co-located environments, we are accustomed to making evaluations based on verbal and non-verbal signals: body language, tone of voice, facial expression, and many more.</description></item><item><title>Onboarding</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</guid><description>The first few months are crucial to the success of the new hire. The newcomer will either buy in by investing their time and attention or treat the company as a paycheck printer, working hard enough not to get fired.
Buddy helps to make onboarding experience engaging, yet well-organized and structured. Work-related information, served in tiny bits in the issue-tracker, facilitates the smooth transition to work culture of a Hygge company.</description></item><item><title>Peer Coaching</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</guid><description>Peer coaching is a form of learning and development where two team-members work together to reflect on current practices; expand, refine, and build new skills; share ideas; teach one another; or solve problems. It&amp;rsquo;s used in some Hygge Companies to improve internal communication and foster personal development of the team-members. These conversations rely on feedback giving and receiving skills.
Peer Coaching Policy Template Every 3 months (Jan 1, Apr 1, Jul 1, Oct 1) we devote some time to self-study and practice feedback during the peer coaching process.</description></item><item><title>Staying Social</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</guid><description>Distributed teams need to work together and communicate intensively. Work is always easier when you know the person you’re communicating with. That’s why Hygge Companies not only encourage personal interactions during team calls, meetups, and workations but also organize Hygge Roulette to foster interpersonal communication.
Team calls Working remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean working alone. To keep everyone involved, Hygge Companies have regular calls where team members share their work and lives.</description></item><item><title>Guiding Principles</title><link>https://hygge.work/guiding-principles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/guiding-principles/</guid><description>Take the initiative It will be difficult to understand how everything works by sitting quietly. There are no marching orders delivered to you on a daily basis, so the only sure way to figure things out is to take the initiative and to talk to people. Ask questions during calls, send messages in the company&amp;rsquo;s chat channels, and reach out to people outside your project for advice. Your colleagues have open calendars.</description></item><item><title>Library</title><link>https://hygge.work/library/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/library/</guid><description>This is a collection of additional resources that might be useful in building a Hygge company.
Handbooks Old Valve Handbook heavily influenced our guiding principles. Valve is a great example of a company that has been pumping out cutting-edge products for decades without becoming a cancerous evil corp. GitLab with its Remote Playbook and Handbook is another place where we stole ideas from. Zapier has a lot of materials about remote work and great tips about internal communication in distributed teams.</description></item><item><title>Personal Project</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-project/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-project/</guid><description>Every newcomer&amp;rsquo;s journey at Hygge Company starts with a personal project. Personal project is a private space to set and track personal milestones. It can take different forms - personal repository or a dashboard, depends on an issue tracker that Hygge company uses.
Enjoy making daily to-do lists? Want to test how markdown on GitHub works? Planning to learn Python from a colleague? Personal project is a powerful tool that satisfies all those needs.</description></item><item><title>Sisu</title><link>https://hygge.work/sisu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/sisu/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire certain types of people: the selection process is designed to spot talented people who are passionate about what they do and ready to hustle to achieve their goals, both personal and professional.
In remote settings, Hygge employees have to learn to manage their resources and energy in a new way. This is why Hygge Companies adopt the concept of good daily sisu to keep their people going.</description></item><item><title>Buddy guidelines</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</guid><description>Visiting another country or hiking an unknown trail all by yourself definitely has its advantages. But if you want to get to know all the local tips and tricks, discover the best view-points and learn fast and safe ways up, you look for local guides.
The same is when you join a new team. A new employee’s onboarding experience is greatly enhanced by buddy who acts as a local guide.</description></item><item><title>Attention Management</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no one to tell you how to organize your day and prioritize important things. Try attention management instead of time management and use time-saving tools and shortcuts.
Priorities Rules, guidelines, principles, people, they all have influence on what you do and how you do it. How do you figure out who to listen to and what to prioritize? Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of things to consider in the order of their importance:</description></item><item><title>Bots</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/bots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/bots/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always a good idea to automate managerial tasks. In your issues, you might encounter several bots that track GitHub&amp;rsquo;s policies compliance.
Stale issue bot - pings an assignee if an issue is not updated. Beware: the stale bot can close issues if you ignore its messages. Tip: Update your issues with any type of the progress.
Required label bot - checks if the issue has all the needed labels.</description></item><item><title>Issue Tracker</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/issue-tracker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/issue-tracker/</guid><description>There are plenty of Issue Trackers and Knowledge Management Systems out there to choose from. For the purpose of simplicity, we&amp;rsquo;ll use GitHub as an example of both. Anyone can set up a free personal (and even an organization) account and start building their Hygge Company using GitHub issue tracker and repositories for free!
Normally, Hygge Companies employees have set tasks and milestones with due dates for all of their projects.</description></item><item><title>Milestones</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</guid><description>Milestone is a SMART goal, that can be split into individual issues for steps and closed at the end of a sprint. It is not a place to collect thematically similar issues (project boards allow to organize your work in many different ways). Ideally, every milestone should be:
Specific – Well defined, clear, and unambiguous. A specific goal has a much greater chance of being accomplished than a general goal.</description></item><item><title>Planning</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</guid><description>Have a plan. However bad it might be. It&amp;rsquo;s much better to come up with a numbered steps plan and ask people to help you to improve it than make them guess or create one for you.
Have troubles making a plan? Try Goal Breakdown Having a big goal with many time-consuming steps can be very stressful, or even overwhelming. This is the type of goal that you will always start &amp;ldquo;tomorrow&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;next week&amp;rdquo;, but those times never seem to come.</description></item><item><title>Project Boards</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/project-boards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/project-boards/</guid><description>Project boards is a managing tool to improve visibility of the work progress. All GitHub projects are located on the organisational level. Use spreadsheets view for Team Projects and kanban view for Personal Projects.
Tip: It is good idea to add a project board in your browser’s bookmark bar, that way you will have quick access.
Personal Boards are there to keep and organize your tasks. Each person is in charge of their own board with collaboration of team manager.</description></item><item><title>Google Workspace</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/google-workspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/google-workspace/</guid><description>Google Workspace is the professional version of GMail, Calendar, Meet, Docs, Team Drive, and much more. Corporate Google account does not only give access to all that ecosystem, but also serves as the key to other web application. The world where you needed to create separate accounts with unique passwords for each application is fading away. It is being replaced with Google and other identity providers that handle your credentials and enforce company-wide policies on application access.</description></item><item><title>Pull Requests</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</guid><description>The pinnacle of mastering the async process is communicating through pull requests.
What is a pull request about?
Pull request is a tool for programmers to sustainably collaborate on code. In a larger context, pull request are useful for suggesting changes policies, wikis, and iteratively collaborating on complex documents. When companies are growing and changing, their approach to work also does: benefits, tools, and best practices are evolving. Before making a change, it&amp;rsquo;s always great to run your ideas by teammates and give others an opportunity to contribute to the final decision.</description></item><item><title>Corporate chats</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/chats/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/chats/</guid><description>Hygge Companies stick to asynchronous communication. This means that out of all the communication channels, they choose those where people don’t have to be present at the same time or in the same space, either physically or virtually.
However, some team-building interactions are meant to be synchronous, such as company chats. Element and Signal are good examples of secure chats. They are great team-building tools that enable water cooler-like conversations and calls.</description></item><item><title>Personal Growth</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire people not only because they are useful now, but also because they believe in their potential.
Working in a Hygge Company provides an opportunity for extremely efficient and, in many cases, very accelerated, career growth. In particular, it provides an opportunity to broaden your skill set well outside the narrow constraints that careers can have at most other companies. There is no red tape, allowing you to tailor your own “growth ladder”.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/security/</guid><description>Nothing will make you 100% safe. The goal is to make the attack prohibitively expensive. Below are the collection of simple tools and steps you can take to make yourself much safer.
To start, use dedicated devices for work or, at least, create a different user profile to isolate work resources from your personal account.
VPN Whether you live in a country that likes to filter traffic or just want to use non-secure WiFi networks, a good VPN is a must.</description></item><item><title>Personal Banking</title><link>https://hygge.work/posts/personal-banking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/posts/personal-banking/</guid><description>Hygge Companies view their employees as responsible adults who can manage not only their work, but also their money. Recent advancements in financial technology brought alternatives to the traditional consumer banking landscape. One way to visualize the key elements of this landscape is imagining a map of interconnected islands where legacy cash-based world borders gen Z contactless payment communities. Although much more complex in reality, this map gives general overview of basic services you can use to receive, store, and spend money anywhere in the world.</description></item><item><title>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks</title><link>https://hygge.work/posts/hygge-benefits/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/posts/hygge-benefits/</guid><description>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks Well-thought benefits packages help Hygge companies retain their top-talents. In this post we shed some light on benefits that Inca Digital offers to their employees.
Effective remote work Being Hygge company, Incas don&amp;rsquo;t track the vacation days and time-off. Incas compensation remains the same even when they are off work for a while, as they don’t get paid for their presence, but for the accomplished tasks.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://hygge.work/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>