<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GitHub on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/tags/github/</link><description>Recent content in GitHub on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bots</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/bots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/bots/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always a good idea to automate managerial tasks. In your issues, you might encounter several bots that track GitHub&amp;rsquo;s policies compliance.
Stale issue bot - pings an assignee if an issue is not updated. Beware: the stale bot can close issues if you ignore its messages. Tip: Update your issues with any type of the progress.
Required label bot - checks if the issue has all the needed labels.</description></item><item><title>Issue Tracker</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/issue-tracker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/issue-tracker/</guid><description>There are plenty of Issue Trackers and Knowledge Management Systems out there to choose from. For the purpose of simplicity, we&amp;rsquo;ll use GitHub as an example of both. Anyone can set up a free personal (and even an organization) account and start building their Hygge Company using GitHub issue tracker and repositories for free!
Normally, Hygge Companies employees have set tasks and milestones with due dates for all of their projects.</description></item><item><title>Milestones</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</guid><description>Milestone is a SMART goal, that can be split into individual issues for steps and closed at the end of a sprint. It is not a place to collect thematically similar issues (project boards allow to organize your work in many different ways). Ideally, every milestone should be:
Specific – Well defined, clear, and unambiguous. A specific goal has a much greater chance of being accomplished than a general goal.</description></item><item><title>Project Boards</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/project-boards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/project-boards/</guid><description>Project boards is a managing tool to improve visibility of the work progress. All GitHub projects are located on the organisational level. Use spreadsheets view for Team Projects and kanban view for Personal Projects.
Tip: It is good idea to add a project board in your browser’s bookmark bar, that way you will have quick access.
Personal Boards are there to keep and organize your tasks. Each person is in charge of their own board with collaboration of team manager.</description></item><item><title>Pull Requests</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</guid><description>The pinnacle of mastering the async process is communicating through pull requests.
What is a pull request about?
Pull request is a tool for programmers to sustainably collaborate on code. In a larger context, pull request are useful for suggesting changes policies, wikis, and iteratively collaborating on complex documents. When companies are growing and changing, their approach to work also does: benefits, tools, and best practices are evolving. Before making a change, it&amp;rsquo;s always great to run your ideas by teammates and give others an opportunity to contribute to the final decision.</description></item></channel></rss>