<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HR processes on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/tags/hr-processes/</link><description>Recent content in HR processes on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/tags/hr-processes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Async</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</guid><description>To get things done, Hygge Companies rely on detailed documentation and atomic iterations that are visible to everyone through issue trackers like GitHub. Mastering this asynchronous workflow is vital to avoiding dysfunction. This is why Hygge companies prefer GitHub issues to chats and video calls. This also means that employees need to ensure that all conclusions made during offline conversations are recorded in GitHub, so that everyone at any time can follow your thought process.</description></item><item><title>Challenge Program</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</guid><description>Challenge program is a perfect tool to discover hidden talent through autonomously vetting potential employees and interns at the start of the hiring process. They consist of issues that can be solved without any access to company resources and require the participants to manage their own work. These projects give interested individuals a chance to prove themselves, learn a bit about our company &amp;amp; products, and produce a useful result in the process.</description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</guid><description>The importance of feedback Human beings are social by nature. Our inclination to change our behavior in reliance upon feedback from our fellows is a primary evolutionary adaptation mechanism. Feedback is our relationship with the world and the world’s relationship with us, it’s how we make an impact on other people. Working in co-located environments, we are accustomed to making evaluations based on verbal and non-verbal signals: body language, tone of voice, facial expression, and many more.</description></item><item><title>Onboarding</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/onboarding/</guid><description>The first few months are crucial to the success of the new hire. The newcomer will either buy in by investing their time and attention or treat the company as a paycheck printer, working hard enough not to get fired.
Buddy helps to make onboarding experience engaging, yet well-organized and structured. Work-related information, served in tiny bits in the issue-tracker, facilitates the smooth transition to work culture of a Hygge company.</description></item><item><title>Peer Coaching</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</guid><description>Peer coaching is a form of learning and development where two team-members work together to reflect on current practices; expand, refine, and build new skills; share ideas; teach one another; or solve problems. It&amp;rsquo;s used in some Hygge Companies to improve internal communication and foster personal development of the team-members. These conversations rely on feedback giving and receiving skills.
Peer Coaching Policy Template Every 3 months (Jan 1, Apr 1, Jul 1, Oct 1) we devote some time to self-study and practice feedback during the peer coaching process.</description></item><item><title>Buddy guidelines</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</guid><description>Visiting another country or hiking an unknown trail all by yourself definitely has its advantages. But if you want to get to know all the local tips and tricks, discover the best view-points and learn fast and safe ways up, you look for local guides.
The same is when you join a new team. A new employee’s onboarding experience is greatly enhanced by buddy who acts as a local guide.</description></item><item><title>Attention Management</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no one to tell you how to organize your day and prioritize important things. Try attention management instead of time management and use time-saving tools and shortcuts.
Priorities Rules, guidelines, principles, people, they all have influence on what you do and how you do it. How do you figure out who to listen to and what to prioritize? Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of things to consider in the order of their importance:</description></item><item><title>Growing</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/</guid><description>Hiring Hygge Companies believe in career choices guided by internal curiosity and the desire to do something meaningful. As intrinsic motivation seems to be one of the keys to happy remote work, Hygge Companies focus attract talent using Challenge and Bar Raiser programs to constantly evolve by hiring only the best people.
Typically, a selection process includes:
Job posting Challenge Submission Up to three interviews Hiring decision and onboarding Hygge Team 🧦☕️ When a team starts growing, you need people to keep everyone cozy and well.</description></item><item><title>Personal Growth</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire people not only because they are useful now, but also because they believe in their potential.
Working in a Hygge Company provides an opportunity for extremely efficient and, in many cases, very accelerated, career growth. In particular, it provides an opportunity to broaden your skill set well outside the narrow constraints that careers can have at most other companies. There is no red tape, allowing you to tailor your own “growth ladder”.</description></item><item><title>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks</title><link>https://hygge.work/posts/hygge-benefits/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/posts/hygge-benefits/</guid><description>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks Well-thought benefits packages help Hygge companies retain their top-talents. In this post we shed some light on benefits that Inca Digital offers to their employees.
Effective remote work Being Hygge company, Incas don&amp;rsquo;t track the vacation days and time-off. Incas compensation remains the same even when they are off work for a while, as they don’t get paid for their presence, but for the accomplished tasks.</description></item></channel></rss>