<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>guru on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/tags/guru/</link><description>Recent content in guru on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/tags/guru/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Challenge Program</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/challenge-program/</guid><description>Challenge program is a perfect tool to discover hidden talent through autonomously vetting potential employees and interns at the start of the hiring process. They consist of issues that can be solved without any access to company resources and require the participants to manage their own work. These projects give interested individuals a chance to prove themselves, learn a bit about our company &amp;amp; products, and produce a useful result in the process.</description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</guid><description>The importance of feedback Human beings are social by nature. Our inclination to change our behavior in reliance upon feedback from our fellows is a primary evolutionary adaptation mechanism. Feedback is our relationship with the world and the world’s relationship with us, it’s how we make an impact on other people. Working in co-located environments, we are accustomed to making evaluations based on verbal and non-verbal signals: body language, tone of voice, facial expression, and many more.</description></item><item><title>Peer Coaching</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</guid><description>Peer coaching is a form of learning and development where two team-members work together to reflect on current practices; expand, refine, and build new skills; share ideas; teach one another; or solve problems. It&amp;rsquo;s used in some Hygge Companies to improve internal communication and foster personal development of the team-members. These conversations rely on feedback giving and receiving skills.
Peer Coaching Policy Template Every 3 months (Jan 1, Apr 1, Jul 1, Oct 1) we devote some time to self-study and practice feedback during the peer coaching process.</description></item><item><title>Library</title><link>https://hygge.work/library/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/library/</guid><description>This is a collection of additional resources that might be useful in building a Hygge company.
Handbooks Old Valve Handbook heavily influenced our guiding principles. Valve is a great example of a company that has been pumping out cutting-edge products for decades without becoming a cancerous evil corp. GitLab with its Remote Playbook and Handbook is another place where we stole ideas from. Zapier has a lot of materials about remote work and great tips about internal communication in distributed teams.</description></item><item><title>Sisu</title><link>https://hygge.work/sisu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/sisu/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire certain types of people: the selection process is designed to spot talented people who are passionate about what they do and ready to hustle to achieve their goals, both personal and professional.
In remote settings, Hygge employees have to learn to manage their resources and energy in a new way. This is why Hygge Companies adopt the concept of good daily sisu to keep their people going.</description></item><item><title>Buddy guidelines</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</guid><description>Visiting another country or hiking an unknown trail all by yourself definitely has its advantages. But if you want to get to know all the local tips and tricks, discover the best view-points and learn fast and safe ways up, you look for local guides.
The same is when you join a new team. A new employee’s onboarding experience is greatly enhanced by buddy who acts as a local guide.</description></item><item><title>Attention Management</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no one to tell you how to organize your day and prioritize important things. Try attention management instead of time management and use time-saving tools and shortcuts.
Priorities Rules, guidelines, principles, people, they all have influence on what you do and how you do it. How do you figure out who to listen to and what to prioritize? Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of things to consider in the order of their importance:</description></item><item><title>Bots</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/bots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/bots/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always a good idea to automate managerial tasks. In your issues, you might encounter several bots that track GitHub&amp;rsquo;s policies compliance.
Stale issue bot - pings an assignee if an issue is not updated. Beware: the stale bot can close issues if you ignore its messages. Tip: Update your issues with any type of the progress.
Required label bot - checks if the issue has all the needed labels.</description></item><item><title>Pull Requests</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</guid><description>The pinnacle of mastering the async process is communicating through pull requests.
What is a pull request about?
Pull request is a tool for programmers to sustainably collaborate on code. In a larger context, pull request are useful for suggesting changes policies, wikis, and iteratively collaborating on complex documents. When companies are growing and changing, their approach to work also does: benefits, tools, and best practices are evolving. Before making a change, it&amp;rsquo;s always great to run your ideas by teammates and give others an opportunity to contribute to the final decision.</description></item><item><title>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks</title><link>https://hygge.work/posts/hygge-benefits/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/posts/hygge-benefits/</guid><description>Inca Digital Benefits and Perks Well-thought benefits packages help Hygge companies retain their top-talents. In this post we shed some light on benefits that Inca Digital offers to their employees.
Effective remote work Being Hygge company, Incas don&amp;rsquo;t track the vacation days and time-off. Incas compensation remains the same even when they are off work for a while, as they don’t get paid for their presence, but for the accomplished tasks.</description></item></channel></rss>