<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tools on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/</link><description>Recent content in Tools on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Google Workspace</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/google-workspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/google-workspace/</guid><description>Google Workspace is the professional version of GMail, Calendar, Meet, Docs, Team Drive, and much more. Corporate Google account does not only give access to all that ecosystem, but also serves as the key to other web application. The world where you needed to create separate accounts with unique passwords for each application is fading away. It is being replaced with Google and other identity providers that handle your credentials and enforce company-wide policies on application access.</description></item><item><title>Corporate chats</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/chats/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/chats/</guid><description>Hygge Companies stick to asynchronous communication. This means that out of all the communication channels, they choose those where people don’t have to be present at the same time or in the same space, either physically or virtually.
However, some team-building interactions are meant to be synchronous, such as company chats. Element and Signal are good examples of secure chats. They are great team-building tools that enable water cooler-like conversations and calls.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://hygge.work/tools/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/tools/security/</guid><description>Nothing will make you 100% safe. The goal is to make the attack prohibitively expensive. Below are the collection of simple tools and steps you can take to make yourself much safer.
To start, use dedicated devices for work or, at least, create a different user profile to isolate work resources from your personal account.
VPN Whether you live in a country that likes to filter traffic or just want to use non-secure WiFi networks, a good VPN is a must.</description></item></channel></rss>