<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>leading on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/tags/leading/</link><description>Recent content in leading on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/tags/leading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Async</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</guid><description>To get things done, Hygge Companies rely on detailed documentation and atomic iterations that are visible to everyone through issue trackers like GitHub. Mastering this asynchronous workflow is vital to avoiding dysfunction. This is why Hygge companies prefer GitHub issues to chats and video calls. This also means that employees need to ensure that all conclusions made during offline conversations are recorded in GitHub, so that everyone at any time can follow your thought process.</description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</guid><description>The importance of feedback Human beings are social by nature. Our inclination to change our behavior in reliance upon feedback from our fellows is a primary evolutionary adaptation mechanism. Feedback is our relationship with the world and the world’s relationship with us, it’s how we make an impact on other people. Working in co-located environments, we are accustomed to making evaluations based on verbal and non-verbal signals: body language, tone of voice, facial expression, and many more.</description></item><item><title>Peer Coaching</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</guid><description>Peer coaching is a form of learning and development where two team-members work together to reflect on current practices; expand, refine, and build new skills; share ideas; teach one another; or solve problems. It&amp;rsquo;s used in some Hygge Companies to improve internal communication and foster personal development of the team-members. These conversations rely on feedback giving and receiving skills.
Peer Coaching Policy Template Every 3 months (Jan 1, Apr 1, Jul 1, Oct 1) we devote some time to self-study and practice feedback during the peer coaching process.</description></item><item><title>Staying Social</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</guid><description>Distributed teams need to work together and communicate intensively. Work is always easier when you know the person you’re communicating with. That’s why Hygge Companies not only encourage personal interactions during team calls, meetups, and workations but also organize Hygge Roulette to foster interpersonal communication.
Team calls Working remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean working alone. To keep everyone involved, Hygge Companies have regular calls where team members share their work and lives.</description></item><item><title>Guiding Principles</title><link>https://hygge.work/guiding-principles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/guiding-principles/</guid><description>Take the initiative It will be difficult to understand how everything works by sitting quietly. There are no marching orders delivered to you on a daily basis, so the only sure way to figure things out is to take the initiative and to talk to people. Ask questions during calls, send messages in the company&amp;rsquo;s chat channels, and reach out to people outside your project for advice. Your colleagues have open calendars.</description></item><item><title>Buddy guidelines</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/buddy-guidelines/</guid><description>Visiting another country or hiking an unknown trail all by yourself definitely has its advantages. But if you want to get to know all the local tips and tricks, discover the best view-points and learn fast and safe ways up, you look for local guides.
The same is when you join a new team. A new employee’s onboarding experience is greatly enhanced by buddy who acts as a local guide.</description></item><item><title>Attention Management</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/attention-management/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no one to tell you how to organize your day and prioritize important things. Try attention management instead of time management and use time-saving tools and shortcuts.
Priorities Rules, guidelines, principles, people, they all have influence on what you do and how you do it. How do you figure out who to listen to and what to prioritize? Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of things to consider in the order of their importance:</description></item><item><title>Bots</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/bots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/bots/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always a good idea to automate managerial tasks. In your issues, you might encounter several bots that track GitHub&amp;rsquo;s policies compliance.
Stale issue bot - pings an assignee if an issue is not updated. Beware: the stale bot can close issues if you ignore its messages. Tip: Update your issues with any type of the progress.
Required label bot - checks if the issue has all the needed labels.</description></item><item><title>Milestones</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/milestones/</guid><description>Milestone is a SMART goal, that can be split into individual issues for steps and closed at the end of a sprint. It is not a place to collect thematically similar issues (project boards allow to organize your work in many different ways). Ideally, every milestone should be:
Specific – Well defined, clear, and unambiguous. A specific goal has a much greater chance of being accomplished than a general goal.</description></item><item><title>Planning</title><link>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/remote-work/planning/</guid><description>Have a plan. However bad it might be. It&amp;rsquo;s much better to come up with a numbered steps plan and ask people to help you to improve it than make them guess or create one for you.
Have troubles making a plan? Try Goal Breakdown Having a big goal with many time-consuming steps can be very stressful, or even overwhelming. This is the type of goal that you will always start &amp;ldquo;tomorrow&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;next week&amp;rdquo;, but those times never seem to come.</description></item><item><title>Project Boards</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/project-boards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/project-boards/</guid><description>Project boards is a managing tool to improve visibility of the work progress. All GitHub projects are located on the organisational level. Use spreadsheets view for Team Projects and kanban view for Personal Projects.
Tip: It is good idea to add a project board in your browser’s bookmark bar, that way you will have quick access.
Personal Boards are there to keep and organize your tasks. Each person is in charge of their own board with collaboration of team manager.</description></item><item><title>Growing</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/</guid><description>Hiring Hygge Companies believe in career choices guided by internal curiosity and the desire to do something meaningful. As intrinsic motivation seems to be one of the keys to happy remote work, Hygge Companies focus attract talent using Challenge and Bar Raiser programs to constantly evolve by hiring only the best people.
Typically, a selection process includes:
Job posting Challenge Submission Up to three interviews Hiring decision and onboarding Hygge Team 🧦☕️ When a team starts growing, you need people to keep everyone cozy and well.</description></item><item><title>Pull Requests</title><link>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/github/pull-requests/</guid><description>The pinnacle of mastering the async process is communicating through pull requests.
What is a pull request about?
Pull request is a tool for programmers to sustainably collaborate on code. In a larger context, pull request are useful for suggesting changes policies, wikis, and iteratively collaborating on complex documents. When companies are growing and changing, their approach to work also does: benefits, tools, and best practices are evolving. Before making a change, it&amp;rsquo;s always great to run your ideas by teammates and give others an opportunity to contribute to the final decision.</description></item><item><title>Personal Growth</title><link>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/growing/personal-growth/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire people not only because they are useful now, but also because they believe in their potential.
Working in a Hygge Company provides an opportunity for extremely efficient and, in many cases, very accelerated, career growth. In particular, it provides an opportunity to broaden your skill set well outside the narrow constraints that careers can have at most other companies. There is no red tape, allowing you to tailor your own “growth ladder”.</description></item></channel></rss>