<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guiding Principles</title><link>https://hygge.work/guiding-principles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/guiding-principles/</guid><description>Take the initiative It will be difficult to understand how everything works by sitting quietly. There are no marching orders delivered to you on a daily basis, so the only sure way to figure things out is to take the initiative and to talk to people. Ask questions during calls, send messages in the company&amp;rsquo;s chat channels, and reach out to people outside your project for advice. Your colleagues have open calendars.</description></item><item><title>Library</title><link>https://hygge.work/library/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/library/</guid><description>This is a collection of additional resources that might be useful in building a Hygge company.
Handbooks Old Valve Handbook heavily influenced our guiding principles. Valve is a great example of a company that has been pumping out cutting-edge products for decades without becoming a cancerous evil corp. GitLab with its Remote Playbook and Handbook is another place where we stole ideas from. Zapier has a lot of materials about remote work and great tips about internal communication in distributed teams.</description></item><item><title>Sisu</title><link>https://hygge.work/sisu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/sisu/</guid><description>Hygge Companies hire certain types of people: the selection process is designed to spot talented people who are passionate about what they do and ready to hustle to achieve their goals, both personal and professional.
In remote settings, Hygge employees have to learn to manage their resources and energy in a new way. This is why Hygge Companies adopt the concept of good daily sisu to keep their people going.</description></item></channel></rss>