<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Communication on Hygge Workbook</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/</link><description>Recent content in Communication on Hygge Workbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hygge.work/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Async</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/async/</guid><description>To get things done, Hygge Companies rely on detailed documentation and atomic iterations that are visible to everyone through issue trackers like GitHub. Mastering this asynchronous workflow is vital to avoiding dysfunction. This is why Hygge companies prefer GitHub issues to chats and video calls. This also means that employees need to ensure that all conclusions made during offline conversations are recorded in GitHub, so that everyone at any time can follow your thought process.</description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/feedback/</guid><description>The importance of feedback Human beings are social by nature. Our inclination to change our behavior in reliance upon feedback from our fellows is a primary evolutionary adaptation mechanism. Feedback is our relationship with the world and the world’s relationship with us, it’s how we make an impact on other people. Working in co-located environments, we are accustomed to making evaluations based on verbal and non-verbal signals: body language, tone of voice, facial expression, and many more.</description></item><item><title>Peer Coaching</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/peer-coaching/</guid><description>Peer coaching is a form of learning and development where two team-members work together to reflect on current practices; expand, refine, and build new skills; share ideas; teach one another; or solve problems. It&amp;rsquo;s used in some Hygge Companies to improve internal communication and foster personal development of the team-members. These conversations rely on feedback giving and receiving skills.
Peer Coaching Policy Template Every 3 months (Jan 1, Apr 1, Jul 1, Oct 1) we devote some time to self-study and practice feedback during the peer coaching process.</description></item><item><title>Staying Social</title><link>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hygge.work/communication/staying-social/</guid><description>Distributed teams need to work together and communicate intensively. Work is always easier when you know the person you’re communicating with. That’s why Hygge Companies not only encourage personal interactions during team calls, meetups, and workations but also organize Hygge Roulette to foster interpersonal communication.
Team calls Working remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean working alone. To keep everyone involved, Hygge Companies have regular calls where team members share their work and lives.</description></item></channel></rss>